                                                                                                                                                                                             >>     /10 Michelle Obama 0
                                                                                                                                                                                                            @MichelleObama




                                                                                                                                                                                                    12:49 PM • Jan 7, 2021

                                                                                                                                                                                     2/2

                                                                                                                                                                                                    7,262 Retweets 416 Quote Tweets


Seeing the gulf between the responses to yesterday's riot and this summer's peaceful protests and the larger movement for racial justice is so 
                                                                                                                                                                                                    47.5K Likes
painful. It hurts. And I cannot think about moving on or turning the page until we reckon with the reality of what we saw yesterday. True progress 

will be possible only once we acknowledge that this disconnect exists and take steps to repair it. And that also means coming to grips with the 

reality that millions voted for a man so obviously willing to burn our democracy down for his own ego.



I hurt for our country. And I wish I had all the solutions to make things better. I wish I had the confidence that people who know better will act like                                                     Tweet your reply         Reply

it for more than a news cycle or two. All I know is that now is a time for true patriotism. Now is the time for those who voted for this president to 

see the reality of what they've supported—and publicly and forcefully rebuke him and the actions of that mob. Now is the time for Silicon Valley                                                            Stuart D... 4, @S... • Jan 7, 2021

companies to stop enabling this monstrous behavior—and go even further than they have already by permanently banning this man from their                                                                    Replying to @MichelleObama
                                                                                                                                                                                                     Alt; ir"Peaceful BLMs protests" this past
platforms and putting in place policies to prevent their technology from being used by the nation's leaders to fuel insurrection.                                                                           summer?? Seriously? Is that what you 
                                                                                                                                                                                                            call arson, looting and mayhem? And I 
And if we have any hope of improving this nation, now is the time for swift and serious consequences for the failure of leadership that led to                                                              dont recall any police shoot,let alone 
                                                                                                                                                                                                            kill, any protestor. Not defending 
yesterday's shame.                                                                                                                                                                                          yesterday,but please don't 
                                                                                                                                                                                                            underestimate the intelligence of 
Thankfully, even in the darkness, there are glimmers of hope. It's something I imagine Reverend Warnock has preached about before—and                                                                       Americans

I'm still heartened beyond belief that he's headed to Washington. I'm glad his fellow Georgian, Jon Ossoff is, too, and that together they'll                                                               nypost.com/2021/01/06/fem.

help give control of Congress back to the only party that's shown that it can put our democracy above its own short-term political fortunes.                                                                                   C2

I pray that every American, especially those who disagree with them, will give our new Congress, President-Elect Biden, and Vice-President- 
                                                                                                                                                                                                                      @Lyn... • Jan 7, 2021 
Elect Harris the chance to lead us in a better direction.                                                                                                                                                !1 Replying to @MichelleObama 
                                                                                                                                                                                                    EILynda... 
                                                                                                                                                                                                            I'm with my forever FLOTUS. And also, 
But make no mistake: The work of putting America back together, of truly repairing what is broken, isn't the work of any individual politician                                                              with Porch Guy.

or political party. It's up to each of us to do our part. To reach out. To listen. And to hold tight to the truth and values that have always led

this country forward. It will be an uncomfortable, sometimes painful process. But if we enter into it with an honest and unwavering love of our 
                                                                                                                                                                                                            Amanda G... Q    • Jan 7, 2021
country, then maybe we can finally start to heal.                                                                                                                                                           Replying to @MichelleObama 
                                                                                                                                                                                                            Thank you.


                                                                                                                                                                                                                                   4

